Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records
Bulk, 1980-2004
1947-2011
WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
55.5 linear feet in 56 record cartoons.
The American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records document the administrative functions of Local 1707/DC 1707 (formerly the Community and Social Agency Employees Union). The Council's jurisdiction covers many categories of employees in private-sector social service agencies. Much of the material in the collection relates to the Council's dealings with agencies where Council members are employed (e.g. bargaining files, contracts, grievance files); the collection also contains Executive Board and Delegate Assembly meeting files; general administrative files for DC 1707, and its locals, committees, and chapters; records of some officers and staff; publications and publicity files; general subject files; as well as photographs and other media formats.
AFSCME. District Council 1707.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The collection was donated to the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Archives, NYU by AFSCME District Council 1707, under an agreement signed by Executive Director Raglan George, Jr., in December 2008. The accession numbers associated with this gift are 2009.005, 2009.012, and 2010.045.
Scope and Content Note
The American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records document the administrative functions of Local 1707/DC 1707, formerly known as the Community and Social Agency Employees Union (CSAE). Much of the material relates to the various agencies where Council members are employed; the collection also contains Executive Board and Delegate Assembly meeting files; general administrative files for DC 1707, and its locals, committees, and chapters; records of some officers and staff; publications and publicity files; and general subject files; as well as photographs and other media formats.
Arrangement
Series I is arranged chronologically; Series II though VI are arranged alphabetically; Series VII and VIII are unprocessed. This collection is organized into eight series:
Series I: Meetings, 1960-2005
Series II: General Administrative and Locals Files, 1950-2006
Series III: Agency Files, 1947-2007
Series IV: Officers and Staff-Administrative Files, 1962-2004
Series V: Publications and Publicity, 1982-2004
Series VI: General Files, 1980-2001
Series VII: Photographs, 1980-2004
Series VIII: Unprocessed Materials
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
District Council 1707 of the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) is the only council within AFSCME that is chartered exclusively to represent private, nonprofit employees. It currently represents about 25,000 workers throughout the New York City area (and New York State), including those within private sector fundraising and advocacy agencies, case work and group work agencies, teaching and related organizations, child care centers, home care services, and Head Start programs. In addition to advocating for better wages, benefits and conditions for employees within these various workplaces, the Council has worked to improve and expand social services in a number of areas. Many Council members work in government-funded private agencies and centers, and, through its Legislative Committee and other advocacy efforts, it has strenuously opposed city and state budget cuts. DC 1707 has also been a strong advocate for children’s welfare since it first began organizing (subsidized) day-care centers in the late 1960s.
The Council began in 1932 as the Association of Federation Workers, a staff association within the Federation of Jewish Philanthropies. Over the ensuing decades, the association had several names and affiliations, including the Community and Social Agency Employees (CSAE), Local 1707. Local 1707 joined the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 in 1955, following the merger of the AFL and the CIO.
Local 1707 outgrew its single local structure by the early 1970s, as a result of growth in membership and its presence in increasingly diverse agencies. A membership referendum approved the establishment of District Council 1707 within AFSCME in December 1973 -- the culmination of a process which took several months. The first DC 1707 officers were nominated and elected in April 1974.
As of 2010, the Council consists of: Local 95 Head Start Employees, Local 107 National Membership and Fund Raising Employees, Local 205 Day Care Employees, Local 215 Social Service Employees, Local 253 Education Employees, Local 389 Home Care Employees, Local 1881 Association of Professional Personnel (Development Corporation for the State of Israel Bonds), and a Retirees Chapter.
DC 1707 also has various committees including the Political Action Committee, the Latino Committee, the Women's Committee, and the Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee. The union has been active throughout its history in advocating for civil rights and has encouraged the political involvement of its membership.
Among the Executive Directors of Local 1707 were Hilda Siff, Shirley Kera, and Benjamin Bially (1963-1968). Executive Director Richard Morton (1970-1984) oversaw the Local’s restructuring into a district council. He was followed by Robert McEnroe (1985-1994) and Josephine LeBeau (1994-2002). Raglan George, Jr. became Executive Director of DC 1707 in 2002, after serving the Council in a number of capacities, including Director of Local 95 and Local 205.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
AFSCME, District Council 37 Records (WAG 265)
AFSCME, District Council 37 Photographs (PHOTOS 247)
AFSCME, District Council 37 Printed Ephemera Collection (PE 020)
AFSCME Printed Ephemera Collection (PE 017)
AFSCME. District Council 1707.; Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (U.S.).; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.).; George, Raglan, Jr.; McEnroe, Robert; Stokely, Brenda; Audiocassettes.; Black-and-white photographs.; Child care workers |z New York (State); Collective bargaining |z New York (State) |z New York.; Collective labor agreements.; Color photographs.; Compact discs.; Contact sheets.; Correspondence.; Financial records.; Grievance arbitration.; Home care services |z United States |x Employees.; Labor unions |z New York (State); Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Minutes.; Negatives (photographic); Nonprofit organizations |x Employees |z United States.; Organization files.; Slides (photographs); Social workers |z New York (State) |z New York.; Videocassettes.
- Series I: Meetings, 1960-2005
  Scope and Content Note
  This series includes material relating to meetings of Local 1707/DC 1707's Executive Board and Delegate Assembly. Executive Board meetings files include reports, activity reports from various officers, staff, and locals, financial records, event flyers, memoranda, constitutions, notes of various board members, schedules, and correspondence. Meetings files often contain minutes for the previous board meeting, and sometimes drafts or copies of minutes for the current meeting. Early Executive Board meetings files (1960s-1970s) are primarily minutes and drafts of minutes with a small amount of supporting documents (agendas, membership reports, attendance sheets). Up to 1973 the Executive Board files usually include material from meetings of the Joint City Council, apparently an early form of the Delegate Assembly.
  Early Delegate Assembly meetings files (1981-1986) consist mostly of minutes and drafts of minutes. Meetings files include agendas, activity reports from various officers, staff and locals, drafts and copies of minutes, (including those of previous meetings), financial statements, event flyers, and attendance sheets.This series contains material pertaining to the administrative functions of Local 1707/DC 1707, its departments, locals, committees and chapters. General administrative material includes correspondence and memoranda, financial records and reports, and items that document Coucil elections, Executive Board, organizing, staff meetings, committees, and other areas. Locals and Retirees Chapter files contain similar material, as well as some trustee board and other meetings files, and records of funds for various locals. General Administrative files are arranged alphabetically by subject; locals follow, arranged by local number. Retirees Chapter material follows locals. DC 1707 locals are: Local 95 Head Start Employees, Local 107 National Membership and Fund Raising Employees, Local 205 Day Care Employees, Local 215 Social Service Employees, Local 253 Education Employees, Local 389 Home Care Employees, Local 1881 Association of Professional Personnel (Development Corporation for Israel).
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board and Joint City Council Meetings, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Oct 4, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Minutes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Feb - Jun 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Sep 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Oct - Nov 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Dec 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Minutes, Jan - Jun 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Jan 14, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Mar 4, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Apr 1, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Meetings, May 6, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes), Sep 10, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes), Oct 7, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Nov 11, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Nov 11, 1997), Dec 8, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Dec 8, 1997), Jan 6, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Meetings (I), Feb 3, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Meetings (II), Feb 3, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Mar - Apr 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Minutes, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Sep - Oct 1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Nov 5, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Dec 8, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Jan 5, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Jan 5, 1999), Feb 8, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Minutes, Feb - Dec 1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Mar 2, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Mar 2, 1999) (I), May 4, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Meetings (II), May 4, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Meetings (III), May 4, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Meetings (IV), May 4, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Financial Statements, May 4, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Jun 8, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - [Executive Board Meetings]: Financial Statements, [Jun 29, 1999] (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Meetings (I), Sep 7, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Meetings (II), Sep 7, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Meetings (I), Oct 5, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Meetings (II), Oct 5, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Meetings (I), Nov 5, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Meetings (II), Nov 5, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Meetings (III), Nov 5, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Financial Statements, [Nov 5, 1999] (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Meetings (I), Dec 14, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Meetings (II), Dec 14, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Meetings (III), Dec 14, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Minutes, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Meetings (I), Feb 1, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Meetings (II), Feb 1, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Mar 7, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Meetings, [May 2, 2000] (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for May 2, 2000), Jun 6, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Minutes, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Mar 20, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Apr 17, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - [Executive Board Meetings], [Oct 2001] (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Minutes, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for May 20, 2002), Sep 5, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Sep 5, 2002), Oct 1, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Oct 1, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Oct 1, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Oct 28, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Oct 28, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Nov 7, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Dec 3, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board Meetings: Minutes, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Jan 7, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Feb 4, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Mar 4, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Apr 15, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Feb 3, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Apr 6, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board Meetings, May 4, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for May 4, 2004), Jun 8, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Dec 7, 2004), Jan 4, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Jan 4, 2005), Feb 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Feb 1, 2005), Mar 1, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Apr 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Apr 5, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Apr 5, 2005), May 3, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for May 3, 2005), Jun 7, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Jun 7, 2005), Sep 8, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Sep 8, 2005), Oct 4, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Oct 4, 2005), Nov 1, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Nov 1, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Meetings (Includes Minutes for Nov 1, 2005), Dec 6, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board Meetings, Dec 6, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Meetings, [Nov - Dec 2005] (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings: Minutes, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings: Minutes, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings: Minutes, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings (Includes Minutes), Jun 27, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Jan 28, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Mar 18, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, May 27, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Sep 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Nov 18, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings: Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, May 2, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Oct 20, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings (Includes Minutes for Oct 20, 1998), Nov 18, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Jan 26, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Feb 22, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Feb 22, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Mar 1999 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Jun 29, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings (Includes Minutes for Sep 7, 1999), Nov 5, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings: Minutes, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings (Includes Minutes), May 8, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings (Includes Minutes for Mar 5, 2002), Sep 17, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings (Includes Minutes for Oct 28, 2002), Nov 7, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Nov 19, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Jan 28, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings, Mar 25, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings (Includes Minutes), Mar 23, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Delegate Assembly Meetings (Includes Minutes), Nov 23, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm: Executive Board/Joint City Council/Delegate Assembly Meetings (2 reels 16 mm microfilm), 1963-1991 (Box 47)
  - Computer Disks and Audiotapes: Executive Board/Delegate Assembly Meetings (5 floppy disks, 3 cassette tapes), 2002-2004 (Box 47)
- Series II: General Administrative and Locals Files, 1950-2006
  This series contains material pertaining to the administrative functions of Local 1707/DC 1707, its departments, locals, committees and chapters. General administrative material includes correspondence and memoranda, financial records and reports, and items that document Coucil elections, Executive Board, organizing, staff meetings, committees, and other areas. Locals and Retirees Chapter files contain similar material, as well as some trustee board and other meetings files, and records of funds for various locals.
  - Administrative Staff Retreat, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - AFL-CIO: Structural Organization, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Agencies, 1997-1998, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1976-2005 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - AFSCME: Affiliate Audit and Review Program, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - AFSCME: "AIDS A Union Contract", Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - AFSCME: Convention, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME: Convention, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME: Convention, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - AFSCME: Convention, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - AFSCME: Financial, 1975-1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - AFSCME: Organizing Convention, Sep 2001 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - AFSCME: Reports, Newsletters, 1993-1998 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - AFSCME: "Stopping Sexual Harassment", Undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Benefits Booklets, [1965], 1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Clerical Staff, 1994-2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Administrative Binder, A-E, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Administrative Binder, F-Z, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Clippings, Flyers, Ephemera, 1996, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Correspondence, Memoranda, 1991-2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Events, 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Events--African-American History Month Celebration, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: General Administrative, 1986-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1991-1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Constitution, circa 1996, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Constitutional Amendments, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Constitutional Convention, Local 1707: Minutes, May 1958 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1993-2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Memoranda, 1997-2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Memoranda, Flyers, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Memoranda, Flyers, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Feb - Apr 1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, May 1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jun 1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jul 1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Aug 1999 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Sep 1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Oct 1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Nov 1999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Dec 1999 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Delegate Assembly: List, [2003] (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Delegate Assembly: Memoranda, 1981-2000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Directors' Reports, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - District Council 1707: General, 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Education Department/Education, 1988-2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Education Department: Memoranda, Flyers, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Election Committee Meeting: Minutes, Mar 1992 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Election Material, 1992-1998, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 10, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 24, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)